export const quiz = {
    heading: 'India - State/Capital Quiz',
    quiz: [
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Gujarat?',
            options: ['Patna', 'Gandhinagar', 'Kohima', 'Ranchi'],
            correctAnswer: 'Gandhinagar'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Madhya Pradesh?',
            options: ['Bhopal', 'Gandhinagar', 'Kohima', 'Ranchi'],
            correctAnswer: 'Bhopal'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Nagaland?',
            options: ['Shilong', 'Itanagar', 'Kohima', 'Chandigadh'],
            correctAnswer: 'Kohima'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Jharkhand?',
            options: ['Hyderabad', 'Kolkata', 'Raipur', 'Ranchi'],
            correctAnswer: 'Ranchi'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Uttarakhand?',
            options: ['Dehradun', 'Lucknow', 'Agartala', 'Shimla'],
            correctAnswer: 'Dehradun'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Himachal Pradesh?',
            options: ['Shimla', 'Ranchi', 'Shilong', 'Raipur'],
            correctAnswer: 'Shimla'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Chattisgadh?',
            options: ['Raipur', 'Bhopal', 'Patna', 'Dispur'],
            correctAnswer: 'Raipur'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Tripura?',
            options: ['Agartala', 'Aizwal', 'Imphal', 'Dispur'],
            correctAnswer: 'Agartala'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Maharashtra?',
            options: ['Mumbai', 'Pune', 'Bombay', 'Nasik'],
            correctAnswer: 'Mumbai'
        },
        {
            question: 'Which is the capital of Bihar?',
            options: ['Ranchi', 'Patna', 'Darbhanga', 'Aara'],
            correctAnswer: 'Patna'
        }
    ]
} 